(Bernadette:)Sure, sometimes.
(Bernadette:)I mean, it can be
a little awkward
(Bernadette:)since I make so much more money
than Howie.
(Howard:)You didn't have to say
"so much more."
(Bernadette:)Well, I didn't have to,
but for the sake of accuracy
(Bernadette:)I felt that I should.
(Howard:)I brought a lot of
significant assets
(Howard:)into the
relationship, too.
(Bernadette:)Like what? Your incomplete set
of Star Trek collector plates?
(Howard:)For your information,
I just bought the last one
(Howard:)I needed on eBay.
(Bernadette:)Without asking me?
(Howard:)There were only three minutes
left in the auction
(Howard:)and it was a mint condition
Scotty from a smoke-free home.
(Bernadette:)How much, Howie?
(Howard:)Not a lot.
(Bernadette:)How much?
(Howard:)Let's not talk about this
in front of our friends.
(Bernadette:)Was it more or less
than falconry school?
(Howard:)For the tenth time,
that was a Groupon.
(Leonard:)Like I would swing
with him.